{
    "id": "554a15877b8841558def39fa0f665479",
    "title": "Two Word Verbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We can’t hold ............................ the meeting any further.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac84d2d1f6c5428eb09010d43b9e7a0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The three gunmen who held ................................... the Union Bank yesterday have been caught.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4992528eef364cf5b4ad8f74119727d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Words for repeated ideas can be left ..................................... in the second of two coordinate clauses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "56ab017998db484c9581ce2a55924629"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge looked ....................................... the papers before announcing the verdict.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c58dcb30afaf4032b0569460ed7ac4ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whenever I come ............................................. an unfamiliar word, I look it up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "upon",
                "across",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d4dd79cb7004ec798eb04030181a734"
        },
        {
            "question": "She knew she was in trouble, so she made ....................................... a story about getting stuck in the traffic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c5ecb096ae34087b5345a6bab747563"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I couldn’t make ...................................... what he was saying, I kept nodding.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0a0eaa293a80419baa92a27493749c48"
        },
        {
            "question": "Pick ...................................... the correct answer from the given options.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0b1c084513954bd4964d740777aa8518"
        },
        {
            "question": "As we drove through the city, our guide pointed ............................. the major tourist attractions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f4fea9d507c04db4bc018b7e671aaaa9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to spend this money. I will put it ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "away",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5988cd991ac4f9e9150d89456924dc2"
        }
    ]
}